{
    "subject": "resource/Mulligan's_Stew",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Mulligan's Stew is comedy/drama television series produced by Paramount Network Television that originally aired as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later, as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977. The series focused on the lives of the Mulligan family. Lawrence Pressman starred as Michael Mulligan, a high school teacher and football coach, and Elinor Donahue played his wife, Jane, who works as a school nurse.",
    "human_readable": "Mulligan' Stew has the comment that it is a comedy/drama television series produced by Paramount Network Television that originally aired as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later, as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977. The series focuses on the lives of the Mulligan family.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9235497713088989,
            "question": "Who produced the television series 'Mulligan's Stew'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887803852558136,
            "question": "What network aired the series version of 'Mulligan's Stew'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8790436387062073,
            "question": "What network aired the initial movie version of 'Mulligan's Stew'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8598254323005676,
            "question": "On what date did 'Mulligan's Stew' originally air as a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8369082808494568,
            "question": "When did 'Mulligan's Stew' transition from a movie to a series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8267821073532104,
            "question": "In what year did 'Mulligan's Stew' originally air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7767598032951355,
            "question": "How long did 'Mulligan's Stew' run as a television series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7617933750152588,
            "question": "What is the central theme of 'Mulligan's Stew'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7426000237464905,
            "question": "What is the main genre of 'Mulligan's Stew'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6787998080253601,
            "question": "What is the duration of each episode in the series format of 'Mulligan's Stew'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mulligan' Stew has the comment that it is a comedy/drama television series produced by Paramount Network Television that originally aired as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later, as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977. The series focuses on the lives of the Mulligan family.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1476_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main genre of 'Mulligan's Stew'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1476_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the central theme of 'Mulligan's Stew'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1476_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long did 'Mulligan's Stew' run as a television series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1476_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1476_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the statement supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe statement \"Mulligan's Stew has the comment that it is a comedy/drama television series produced by Paramount Network Television that originally aired as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later, as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977. The series focuses on the lives of the Mulligan family.\" is supported by multiple documents, specifically:\n\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1476/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1476/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt\n\nBoth of these documents contain information that confirms the statement, therefore the output is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided documents confirm that Mulligan's Stew is a comedy/drama television series produced by Paramount Network Television, which originally aired as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977. The documents also state that the series focuses on the lives of the Mulligan family."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}